

PROFILE INFO

Web Designer

Highly self-motivated and goal-oriented Web Designing Engineer with 6 years of experience as Assistant Professor looking for an opportunity that flexes my skills. Re-entering the workforce after taking few years off to raise a children while staying engaged with the industry through occasional freelance work.

SWATI ANANTWAR

WEB DESIGNER

Phone: (+352) 661-4545-77

Email: swatianantwar@gmail.com

Address: Esch-Sur- Azette, Luxembourg.

GitHub: https://swatianantwar-

portfolio.netlify.app/

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Padagogy
- Problem Solving
- Mentorship
- Time Management
- Team Player
- Positive Attitude
- Written and Verbal communication

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Selenium
- Web Designing
- JAVA/C++
- HTML5/CSS
- Oracle/MySql

PROJECTS

- Data Integrity And Security In Cloud - Linux and JAVA
- Weather crop Management .Net
 MySql
- Student Information System -.Net, Mysql
- Weather temperature recording -C++
- Student Information System- java,
 MySQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

2009 - 2016 ASSISTANT PROFESSOR, HVPM ENGINEERING INSTITUTE, AMRAVATI, INDIA

- Instrumental in department planning and operations as well as development and implementation of university policies and laws
- Initiated, facilitated, and moderated computer sciencerelated course discussions in accordance with curriculum
- Planned, designed, and revised syllabi, curriculum, instruction content, and other materials as required
- Provided student body with counsel and direct supervision in laboratory work and issues with coursework
- Stayed abreast of advancements in computing, technology, programming, and syntax

2016 - 2020 UNITED STATES

- Full Time Parent
- Roller Skating Coach in New Jersey.
- Personal Tutor for "SANKSKRIT" [Ancient Indian Language].
- "Event Manager", I was helping my friend in arranging events in New Jersey.
- 2020 2023 LUXEMBOURG
 - Family Project
 - Completed ICT two weeks training.(HTML5, CSS3, Java Script)

EDUCATION

JUL 2004

JUL 2008

AUG 2013 POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN MANAGEMENT
MAY 2016 IN IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Welingker Institure of Management, Mumbai

JUL 2014 MASTER'S OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER
JUL 2016 SCIENCE & ENGG

S.G.B.A. University, Maharastra, India

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INFORMATION
TECHNOLOGY

S.G.B.A. University, Maharastra, India

EXTRA ACTIVITIES

- Mentor Of 120 Girls in HVPM COET
 Hostel (Hostel In charge) and member
 of AntiRagging committee.
- Youth Festival Manager of H.V.P.M.C.O.E.T of Amravati University in 2012
- Active member Of "ANKUR" Social Service Institute.
- Awarded with 'BEST PERSNALITY OF THE COLLEGE -2008' and GIRLS REPRESENTATIVE of IT section(2007-08)
- Active member of "NSS" (NATIONAL SOCIAL SERVICE).
- University Badminton Player (Amravati University) From 2004-2010.

HOBBIES

- Painting
- Badminton/Roller skating
- Cooking

PUBLISHED PAPERS

Paper published in International Journal / National Conference

- "Data Integrity And Security In Cloud" in International Journal IJARCET, in Volume 1, Issue7, on 7 Sept 2012.(ISSN -2278-1323)
- "Cloud Computing and Security Models: A Survey" in IJESIT of volume 1, Issue 2, in Nov 2012 (ISSN-2319-5967)
- "Simplified Approach of Artificial Neural Network: Strengths And Weaknesses" in IJEIT of volume 1, Issue 4, (ISSN-2277-3754)
- "Methodology For Data Mining" in IJCSCSE. of volume 2, Issue 4, (ISSN-2277-9477)
- Presented project in International Conference on "Ball Tracking" during 15th to 17th Jan 2013
- Paper presented on "Analysis And Innovations in Content Based or multimedia Search Engine" in National Conference on Information And Communication Tech.
- Secured 1st position in E-Vidya National Level Technical paper presentation Event in 2007.